First of all let me show you how the plan
works.  Rohit will go to gerat.com.
Click here to know about Health Insurance Plans ICICI LB.  ICC's
plans will start showing.  Now, in our ICICI LBD
Elevate plan of Rs 5 crore, we will go to the
policy wording.  Open
now will do wellness in the search above.
So here it comes.  Now it will show
how many points are given for which thing.
Health Assessment You can see all this.
Now let me take you to the app and see how
it all works.  You will need to install three apps.
One is the Il Take Care
Insurance App.  ICIC is an application of LB.
Second Google Fit activity tracking.
Third, Google Health Connect.  You will have to install these three apps
first.  Now
when you install the app,
you will have to allow all the permissions.  Please allow all permissions on Google FIT,
Google Health Connect and ICICI I Will
Take Care app.  Only
then will the app connect and your
data will keep getting recorded, including step
count etc.  Then after that you will open the app
of ICIC I will take care app.   We will go to the
benefits below.
Now earn points here, like I have
earned 800 points in it right now.  Now
click on Earn Points.  In this you will
see everything that you have to do.
Like fitness challenge, in this
you will get two fitness challenges worth 250 points.  Like
clicked on Take a Challenge.  What do you have to do in this
?  Squads will have to be completed.
It says 10 Squads
Jumping Jacks Street Post.  Now what is this
?  How does it happen?  You
can search this YouTube video.  Search any YouTube channel
on YouTube or by searching on Google.
Search chat on GBT.
You will get it.
How to do all this.  It is easy.  It will be done quickly
and you will get your 500 points
in it.  Second face scan.  Whenever means every
quarter you have to scan your face once every 3 months.
By scanning your face, it tells you all the data like your
heart reading or your stress level.
It scans all those things.
Like I did it once and I got
100 points.  Now I will do it again after 3 months,
then I will come.  Like Step
Count
Daily, these step counts are running in it.
Step count: This is done through the Google app.
Like I have installed Google Fit app.
In this, I have taken
3211 steps till now since morning.
There is a target for daily step count.  So if
you complete 8-8000 steps on any 20 days in the entire month,
then
you will become eligible for this.  You will get 500 points for
that month.
So like right now I have 3200 and so on.  It will become 8000.  I get
my daily meals.  You
can see that the entire data is showing in it.
How many months have passed for me so far?  Weekly,
every day I complete 8000 steps.  If
not, shake the phone slightly with your hand.
Rotate it like a drum or
give it to someone who is going out, he will keep
walking with the phone in his pocket or hand for some time, his
steps will be counted through it,
8000 daily steps will be done, it is not a big deal,
then these points are of different types
like Chat with X Expert, there is
an expert of their ICC who is some MBBS type
doctor type who
will consult you once and
can ask about your health condition etc.
I have not done it yet but this is what is going to happen,
it is simple in this, it does
not matter what your answer is, you will get
100 points by chatting with an expert and doing
health risk assessment. I have already
given this test. Some general questions are
asked in this, what do you follow in your daily activities,
what do you eat, walk, do
yoga, exercise, what all do you do in your
daily routine and there is
one more question which
also asks about your family history, whether
anyone in your family has hypertension,
diabetes or any other disease,
that option is also available.  So this
health assessment has to be done once in a while.  Then
after that you get these points.
Click on Earn Points.  He will come
inside again.
Then comes the health quiz.  Health quiz also contains
simple normal questions.  You have to
pay this once a year.
You will earn this also.  Like whatever I have written has come,
whatever has happened is coming as complete and is being written.
In this also, Earn is written above in Health Risk Assessment.
Then there is this health
events option.  Health events means
you should look at any one of
these three-four events as it is written, Walkathon, Marathon, Cyclothon, I do
n't know about Cyclothon, Smarthon, but marathons keep happening from time to time, they happen
in many cities, in Delhi,
Mumbai, etc., in different cities,
so you should look at the marathons near you,
when are the events coming, search on Google,
watch on YouTube, you will get to know,
they keep happening,
you have to participate in it once,
you should have a certificate of marathon participation, you
just have to upload that certificate in it
and you will get points.
Health checkup report.  You get 1000 points in this.
You can get it done from any lab near your home.  There will be 1000 points
in this.  And there is no such thing
as which tests you should have.
Like blood test, urine test,
KFT, LFT, thyroid, vitamins,
calcium etc. there is nothing like that.
You should also get your blood test done to check if it is normal.  There are
different types of packages, you can get them done for Rs
200, 300, 400.  This will
also be your health test and if you
upload its reports, you will
get 1000 points.  Mainly your points will
come from step count.  6000 points
come from the year's step account.
You can earn a total of 9400 points in the whole year.  Out of
those 9400 points, 6000
come from step count only.  500 points every month, as
I told you,
you will have to do 8-8000 steps for 20 days in a month.  If you do fewer
steps, for example, if it is 6000, then you will
get fewer points.  You will get 300, you will
get 350.  There are some like this.  But you can do it for Rs 8000.
This will happen.  You will
get a full 30% discount on this at the time of renewal.
I am using this app completely.  I am
using it completely and my
health is good.  This is not just about discounts.
If we follow this then it
is beneficial for our health.  It's
good for us.  And some new things get
to be seen.  If you participate in marathons etc., you will
get some new entertainment.  You will get to see something new and learn something new.